Happy juve morning to all my Grenadians.
We are in the thick of carnival right now in Grenada.
My helmet says Jeb Jeb.
If you don't know what this is about, it's all good.
Want to remind you, you can catch me on stage in Harlem this Wednesday.
Come through the uptown.
I know some of y'all miss me being on stage, being funny.
I'm back on stage being funny and teaching about energy work.
We bring music into the show.
It's a really beautiful experience.
Big up all my Grenadians.
Wishing you a happy juve.
Get your energy right.
Come and join me, Amanda Seals, this Wednesday, August 12th,
and every second Wednesday at Comedy in Harlem for Radical Rhythms Experience.
Every month we come together to level up our vibration with music, humor, and each other.
Tickets available at comedyinharlem.com.